ANTARI DWIJAYANTI

Denpasar, Bali • (+62) 85157734785 • antaridwijayanti@gmail.com www.antaridwijayanti.com

SUMMARY

Web Developer with over 2 years of experience in designing, developing, and maintaining web applications using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and PHP (Laravel). I combine UI/UX principles with programming skills to create responsive, user-friendly, visually appealing interfaces, and focus on performance optimization. Currently eager to expand my skills in React.js and other frontend technologies

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Developer, PT. Grune Teknologi Indonesia (Full-time)

Dec 2024 - Current

- Developed web applications for clients primarily using HTML, CSS, Laravel Inertia, React.js, and TypeScript
- Performed quality assurance of web applications by conducting unit testing in Laravel.

Web Developer, PT. APPKEY (Full-time)

Jul 2022 - Oct 2024

- Developed and maintained web applications with responsive interface using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript (jQuery), and PHP (Laravel).
- Integrated RESTful APIs into web applications
- Implemented third-party services APIs for client web applications, including Square Payment Gateway, Midtrans
 Payment Gateway, and Google Place API.
- Developed RESTful APIs for mobile application using PHP (Laravel)
- Developed a mobile application using Flutter and achieving 100+ downloads on the Play Store

Web Developer, Kayana Creative (Internship)

April 2022 - July 2022

- Independently designed and developed a waste management web application for Ungasan village utilizing HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript (jQuery), and PHP (Laravel).
- Built a responsive and user-friendly interface for four user roles: client, waste collector, accounting, and administrator
- Presented the project to stakeholders, delivering a live demo of the web application to showcase its features

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Information System ITB STIKOM Bali

July 2022

• GPA: 3.84

SKILLS

- Programming Languages: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, PHP, TypeScript, Dart
- Frameworks/Libraries: JQuery, AJAX, React, Next.js, Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS, Laravel, Flutter
- Tools & Platforms: Git, GitHub, GitLab, Vercel, Figma, Adobe XD, Bitbucket, Canva
- Languages: English (Intermediate), Indonesia (Native)

CERTIFICATES

- React The Complete Guide 2024 (Incl. NextJS, Redux) | Udemy | Dec 2024
- Software Development Skema Programmer | Badan Nasional Sertifikasi Profesi (BNSP) | Feb 2021
- Skilvul Virtual Internship: UX Challenges | Skilvul | Dec 2021
- Database Design & Programing with SQL | Digital Talent Scholarship | Oct 2021

SELECTED PROJECTS

Ginza Golf E-Commerce (Freelance)

Aug 2024 - Dec 2024

- Contributed to the front-end development by of a web-based e-commerce platform for golf equipment by troubleshooting, resolving issue, and updating features according client's requests
- Utilizing React.js, Next.js, TypeScript, and Tailwind CSS.

antaridwijayanti.com (Personal Project)

June 2024

- A personal portfolio website featuring a minimalist design that is fully responsive across all devices.
- Contributed to both the design and development using Figma, React.js, Next.js, and Tailwind CSS.

May 2024

Bali Bagus Rentcar Web Application (Freelance)

- · Car rental website with SEO best practices implemented and engaging interface for both user and admin side
- Contributed to both the design and development using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, and PHP (Laravel).

March 2023

MenuMate QR Code Menu Ordering System (PT. APPKEY Internal Project)

• Contributed as a front-end developer to build the customer side of menu ordering web application using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, and JQuery. Fully responsive across mobile, tablet, and desktop devices.